welcome to another tutorial in this
欢迎使用本教程中的另一个教程
video we'll be learning about the
我们将在视频中了解
different selection tools we have
我们有不同的选择工具
available in for selecting certain
在中可用于选择某些
areas of our image and creating a custom
我们形象的区域和创建自定义
selection that we can then apply changes
然后我们可以应用更改的选定内容
to so this is common if we want to only
所以这很常见 如果我们只想
apply changes in here like you race for
在此应用更改 就像您竞相
example it'll only erase to wherever we
例如 它只会擦除到我们的任何位置
have selected any of our brushes will
已经选择了我们的任何一把刷子
only be drawn in this selection this is
仅在此选择中绘制这是
also pretty common for doing something
做某事也是很常见的
like a color effect where you'll select
就像一种颜色效果 你可以选择
just a certain area and we can go to
只有一个特定的区域 我们可以去
like hue and saturation and change the
例如色调和饱和度 并更改
hue of whatever selected in that area
该区域中选定的任何内容的色调
also what you'll do a lot is you'll do a
另外 您要做的是做一个
rectangular selection like this and then
像这样的矩形选择 然后
you can go to image crop to selection
您可以转到图像裁剪以进行选择
and sort of cut out or you could get a
或者你可能会得到一个
really tight shot in here of just these
在这里拍得很紧 只有这些
strawberries and we can go to crop a
我们可以一起去种草莓
selection and then you'll just have this
选择 然后你就会得到这个
image we could then export or do
然后我们可以将图像导出或执行
something to so let me do ctrl Z and
一些事情让我来做ctrl Z和
undo all of this and let's start from
取消所有这些 让我们从
the very beginning learning how to use
一开始就学习如何使用
these selection tools the first tool
这些选择工具是第一个工具
we're going to look at is the
我们要看的是
rectangular Select tool R is the
矩形选择工具R是
shortcut key to get into that tool and
快捷键进入该工具并
that just lets us draw a rectangle or a
这只允许我们绘制一个矩形或一个
square to draw it we just left we hold
画出它的方块我们刚刚离开我们拿着
down the left mouse button and then
按下鼠标左键 然后
unhold it to create the selection once
取消按住它可创建一次选定内容
it's created we can change it by
它是被创建的 我们可以通过以下方式更改它
hovering to the top and changing how
徘徊在顶端 改变着如何
tall it is either at the top or the
它要么高 要么高 要么高
bottom and I'm just left clicking and
底部 我只需点击左键
holding to change that again that only
坚持再次改变这一点 只是
appears when you get close towards the
当您靠近
edge sort of those handles will appear
将显示这些手柄的边缘排序
for doing that you can go to the corner
要做到这一点 你可以去拐角处
and change the corners as well and so
也要改变转角等等
the bottom left-hand corner is now fixed
左下角现在已修复
and the other two are changed here if I
另外两个在这里更改 如果我
click on the left one the bottom
点击左下角
right-hand corner is fixed and
右下角是固定的
everything else has changed so you can
其他一切都改变了 所以你可以
use these methods to sort of select the
使用这些方法来排序选择
part of the image you want with a
您需要的图像的一部分
rectangular selection if we want to move
如果要移动 请选择矩形
the entire selection around we can use
我们可以使用周围的整个选择
the Move tool so we click on the move
移动工具 所以我们点击移动
tool by default I believe it's set to
工具默认情况下 我认为它设置为
moving the layer you have the entire
移动您拥有的整个层
layer so it's going to kind of move our
所以它会移动我们的
image and we see this transparency in
图像 我们在图中看到这个透明度
the background I'm gonna hit control Z
我要点击Ctrl Z键的背景
to get it back because what I want to do
去找回它 因为我想做的是
to move the selection we see under the
要移动我们在
settings for move it have
Move It的设置有
it has an option for moving just the
它有一个选项 只移动
selection so I'll left click on that and
选择 我将左键单击它 然后
now when I move this around it'll move
现在 当我移动它时 它也会移动
my selection and not my image so I can
我的选择而不是我的形象 所以我可以
move this down to the part of the image
把这个向下移到图像的那部分
I want and maybe I'll just go to image
我想 也许我会去IMAGE
crop to selection to get that nice
裁剪到精选 以获得如此好的效果
selected area so now we can either work
选定的区域 所以现在我们可以
on our image just having the whole thing
在我们的形象上只有整件事
selected if you notice the whole part is
如果您注意到整个部分是
still selected right now we can see
仍处于选中状态 现在我们可以看到
these little black and white lines
这些小黑白线条
moving around the outside and that shows
在外面走来走去 这表明
us everything is selected which means
美国一切都被选中了 这意味着
any tools that we use right now we're
我们现在使用的任何工具都是
going to apply to the entire image but
将应用于整个图像 但是
if we only wanted to select a certain
如果我们只想选择某个
area like the strawberry we might use
就像我们可能会用到的草莓
this next tool which is the ellipse
下一个工具是椭圆
select tool it's going to let us draw an
选择工具 它将让我们绘制一个
ellipse or a circle similar to the
椭圆或类似于
rectangular tool we just left click and
我们刚刚点击的矩形工具
hold and whatever selection we draw it
Hold和我们绘制的任何选区
draws a new selection every time so if
每次都绘制一个新的选区 因此如果
we want to apply some smudges to just
我们想要将一些污点应用到
this part of the strawberry we select
我们选择草莓的这一部分
this we can come over and resize the
这个我们可以过来调整大小
circle similar to we did like how we did
圆圈类似于我们所做的 就像我们所做的那样
with the rectangle and then we can come
带着长方形 然后我们就可以来了
and grab the smudge tool and now only
然后抓起涂抹工具 现在只有
smudging is going to happen within our
污迹将在我们的
selected area and nothing outside will
选定的区域和外部的任何内容都不会
be affected I mean it ctrl Z to undo
受影响 我的意思是按Ctrl Z来撤销
those changes if we want to select
如果我们想要选择
multiple strawberries or multiple parts
多个草莓或多个部分
of our image we can grab this tool any
我们可以在任何时候获取这个工具
of these tools have these options and
这些工具中有这些选项和
under mode just like we changed with the
在模式下 就像我们使用
Move mode there's also this ellipse
移动模式还有这个椭圆形
select mode right now it says replace
立即选择模式 它会显示替换
the current selection but we could also
当前的选择 但我们也可以
go add to current selection when we're
当我们处于以下状态时 转到添加到当前选择
in this mode anything we draw will get
在此模式下 我们绘制的任何内容都将
added to it and create sort of this
添加到其中 并创建了类似于
different shape I can create like a
我可以创建不同的形状 就像
snowman shape here but then we have this
雪人的形状在这里 但我们有这个
part selected over here as well so I
在这里也选择了零件 所以我
could select every strawberry
我可以选择每一种草莓
individually like this and then we have
像这样的个人 然后我们就有了
a nice sort of selection of just our
一种精选的我们的
strawberries there's also part of the
草莓在那里也是
mode that lets us subtract from the
模式 该模式允许我们从
current selection so if I didn't want if
当前选择 所以如果我不想
I wanted to change this I just kind of
我想改变这一点 我只是有点
draw and subtract this out this isn't
画出并减去这个 这不是
necessarily the best way to do this but
当然这是最好的办法 但是
it is a method of doing it and if you're
这是一种这样做的方法 如果你
selecting a kind of a circular object it
选择一种圆形对象 它
can be kind of nice like this bucket
可以像这个水桶一样漂亮
here we can select this and sort of
在这里 我们可以选择这个 然后
cut out part everything that's not
剪掉所有不是的部分
within this selection so that's just a
在这个选择中 所以这只是一个
method for doing this election we hit
我们找到了做这场选举的方法
enter and we can have that be our total
进入 我们可以得到这是我们的总数
selection and then anything that we
选择 然后是任何我们
apply within here is going to be only
在此范围内的申请将仅限于
applied to that selected area the next
应用于下一个选定区域
tool we'll look at is the freehand
我们将看到的工具是写意
selection tool this lets us let click
选择工具这让我们可以点击
with our mouse to create these points
用我们的鼠标来创建这些点
and we can create any type of custom
我们可以创建任何类型的定制
shape we want when we get to the end
当我们走到尽头时 我们想要的形状
we'll just click on the very last point
我们只需点击最后一点
and then we can come in here and adjust
然后我们可以到这里来调整
by left clicking and holding and adjust
通过左键单击并按住并调整
these to get just the shape that we want
这些正好是我们想要的形状
when we think we have it right we'll hit
当我们认为我们做得对的时候 我们就会击中
enter and that becomes our selected area
进入 这将成为我们选择的区域
we can then use any tool that we want to
然后 我们可以使用任何我们想要的工具
to apply changes only within the
将更改仅应用于
selected area and nothing outside will
选定的区域和外部的任何内容都不会
be affected I want to also bring your
受影响我也想带上你
attention to the different options on
注意上的不同选项
these tools we have this feathered edge
这些工具 我们有这个羽毛边缘
and what the feathering helps you do is
而羽毛能帮你做的是
if you're ever doing something maybe we
如果你想做点什么 也许我们
draw a circle here just to show this if
在这里画一个圈 只是为了显示这一点
we grab a brush and right now we just
我们拿起刷子 现在我们只是
fill the whole thing in with black we
用黑色的WE填充整个房间
see it has a very hard edge but if we
看 它有一个非常硬的边缘 但如果我们
turn on feathering so I'll grab the
打开羽化 这样我就可以抓住
ellipse tool again and we'll check this
再次使用椭圆工具 我们将检查此工具
feather edges
羽毛边
what feather edges does is create a
羽化边所做的是创建一个
softer edge around the selected area so
选定区域周围的边缘更柔和 因此
now if we grab the brush tool and fill
现在 如果我们抓住画笔工具并填充
this in we see the edges are much softer
在这个图中 我们看到边缘要柔和得多
we don't have a hard edge like we did on
我们不像上一次那样有强硬的优势
this one so if I go to select I can
这一个 所以如果我去选择 我可以
right click and go to select all so now
右键单击并转到选择All so Now
we see without the selection on these we
我们看到 如果没有这些选择 我们将
have a soft edge here a feathered edge
这里有一个柔软的边缘 有羽毛的边缘
on this selection and no feather on this
在这个选择上 在这个上没有羽毛
one so the feather can kind of help you
这样羽毛就能帮到你
merge in and make it look more natural
融入其中 让它看起来更自然
without a hard edge on it and again
没有坚硬的边缘 一次又一次
that's feathering and it's a good idea
这就是羽毛 这是个好主意
to go through and play with the
要通过并使用
different options anti-aliasing also
不同的抗锯齿选项也不同
helps smooth the edges out around your
帮助平滑您周围的边缘
selected area when you have something
当您拥有某些东西时 选择区域
selected as well we can change the
我们也可以更改
position of a selection here by just
此处选定内容的位置只需
manually if we know where we want it to
如果我们知道要将其放置在何处 请手动操作
be on the pixels we can change the size
在像素上 我们可以改变大小
of it this way as well and so there's
它也是这样的 所以有
some really good options we can play
一些非常好的选择 我们可以玩
with under the properties of each
在每个对象的属性下
different selection method we control Z
我们控制Z的不同选择方法
and get back another selection method I
找回另一种选择方法--
want to show is
想要展示的是
this similar to the freehand selection
这类似于手绘选择
we're gonna skip a few this is the
我们将跳过几个 这是
scissor selection and it does similar to
剪刀选择 它的功能类似于
freehand only it's more intelligent so
只是写意更聪明 所以
we just left-click and we can come over
我们只需左键点击 我们就可以过来
here and left-click again and it's gonna
单击此处并再次左击 它将显示
try and estimate where we want what part
试着估计我们想要什么部件
of the object we want to follow it
我们想要跟随它的对象的
didn't do a great job in this case but
在这个案子里做得不是很好 但是
it'll kind of try to follow some of the
它会尝试遵循一些
lines around and then we can always come
排起了长队 然后我们随时都可以来
in here and re-click an add one in to
在此处并重新单击添加一项到
get it exactly where we want and again
一次又一次地把它放在我们想要的地方
we hit the enter key and now we have
我们按了Enter键 现在我们已经
this part of the image selected we could
我们可以选择图像的这一部分
do something like ctrl C on the keyboard
在键盘上做一些类似Ctrl C的操作
to copy this and then we can get if we
复制这个 然后我们可以得到如果我们
were in a new document we can go control
在我们可以控制的新文件中
V and paste just that part of the image
V并仅粘贴图像的该部分
but we see it is kind of jagged because
但我们看到它有点参差不齐 因为
we didn't have a feather applied so we
我们没有涂上羽毛 所以我们
might want to apply a feather to that
可能会想要在这上面加一层羽毛
instead I'm gonna close out of this or
取而代之的是我要结束这一切否则
we could make a change to it we can just
我们可以做些改变 我们可以
do some adjusting in here if we did try
如果我们真的试过了 在这里做一些调整
to crop if we went to image crop to
如果我们转到图像裁剪以进行裁剪
selection just be aware it's gonna
精选只需意识到它会
always crop a square it's not going to
总是修剪一个正方形 它不会
cut it out to cut it out we'd want you
停下来 停下来 我们会想要你
to use something under edit so we can
使用正在编辑的内容 以便我们可以
right click and go to edit and we can do
右键单击并进入编辑 我们可以执行以下操作
cut we can actually cut this and remove
我们实际上可以把这个切下来 然后移走
it and have a blank space in there we
它和我们在那里有一个空白区域
can right click and go to edit we can go
可以右击并转到编辑我们可以转到
fill with so we can fill with the
填充 这样我们就可以填充
foreground color similar to using the
前景颜色类似于使用
bucket tool there's lots of different
铲斗工具有很多不同之处
options and we'll play with more of that
选项 我们将尝试更多选项
in the future these other ones if I'm
在未来这些其他的如果我是
going to go to select and go to all
我要去选择 然后去全部
these other ones here we have and your
我们这里还有其他的 还有你的
icons may look different we have the
图标可能看起来不同 我们有
fuzzy select and the select by color
模糊选择与颜色选择
they're gonna kind of behave similar in
他们会表现出类似的行为
this one select by color does what you
这个按颜色选择的选项可以执行以下操作
might expect where if you select a
如果您选择一个
certain color it selects everything
特定的颜色 它可以选择一切
within that color and so we can turn
在那个颜色里 所以我们可以
this threshold down over here to the
这个门槛从这里一直延伸到
left and then it will select much finer
向左 然后它会选择更精细的
it really helps you have if you have a
它真的对你有帮助如果你有
good solid color you're trying to select
您要选择的纯色很好
otherwise it's gonna try to grab more
否则 它会试图夺取更多
like it's getting this sort of greens
就像它得到了这样的绿色
and tans in the bucket and in the leaves
在桶里和树叶里晒黑
the fuzzy select is going to help us get
模糊选择将帮助我们获得
away from that problem turn down the
远离那个问题 转弯
threshold a little bit it's hard to tell
门槛有点小 很难说
with this example but it really is only
在这个例子中 但它实际上只是
if we
如果我们
our threshold right we can then select
我们的门槛权利 然后我们可以选择
just a certain area and just make
只是一个特定的区域 只是让
changes to just those leaves or just
只更改那些树叶 或者只是
these parts of the strawberries but
草莓的这些部分 但是
again it's not perfect like we had there
再说一次 它不像我们在那里那样完美
certain pixels are going to select
某些像素将选择
different shaded areas especially
特别是不同的阴影区域
gradients and shading so it may or may
渐变和着色 因此它可能或可能
not work depending on the image you're
不工作取决于你的形象
using anyway that's some of the
不管怎么说 这是一些
different selection methods you can play
您可以选择不同的选择方法
with we'll touch more on these ones
接下来我们将更多地讨论这些问题
they're a little bit more advanced so
他们更先进一点 所以
we'll touch more on using the threshold
我们将更多地讨论如何使用门槛
and playing with some of these in the
在这里玩其中的一些
future there's also ways we can combine
未来也有我们可以结合在一起的方式
different ones but just be aware of the
不同的 但只要意识到
selection mode is really important and
选择模式非常重要 而且
if you do get on the mode one common
如果你真的进入了模式 一个常见的
mistake is that if you go to cut
错误的是 如果你去切
something out and you cut the whole
把一些东西剪掉 然后把整个剪掉
thing out and then you forget you were
然后你就忘了你是
in that mode and you go to draw a
在该模式下 您将绘制一个
selection it won't let you it just gives
它不会给你选择 它只会给你
you this symbol you can always look for
你这个符号 你总能找到
cues down at the bottom if something's
如果有什么东西在底部 就会有提示
not working it tells us cannot subtract
不工作它告诉我们不能减去
from an empty selection it's because
从空的选择中 这是因为
we're on the subtraction mode right now
我们现在处于减法模式
one thing I like to do is just stay in
我喜欢做的一件事就是呆在家里
this mode here the replaced current
此模式在这里被替换的电流
selection mode and then use the shortcut
选择模式 然后使用快捷键
keys we can hover over and learn those
我们可以将鼠标悬停在这些键上学习
shift and control so if in this mode we
移位和控制 因此如果在此模式下
draw and we draw again
抽签 我们再抽签
it replaces our selection holding shift
它取代了我们的选择按住Shift
we can add to that without having to go
我们可以在不必离开的情况下添加这些内容
and change the mode so we can add to our
并更改模式 以便我们可以添加到我们的
selection and holding ctrl we can
可以选择并按住Ctrl键
subtract to that and that works with all
减去这一点 它就适用于所有
these different ones we can do freehand
这些不同的我们可以手绘
hold shift and add in a new part and hit
按住Shift键并添加新零件 然后点击
enter so we can add in different parts
输入 这样我们就可以添加不同的部分
if we want to if we can freehand draw in
如果我们想要 如果我们能写意画进去
these and then we could freehand draw
这些然后我们就可以手绘了
out some of the selection as well so it
也拿出一些精选 这样就好了
can be really handy so learn those
可以非常方便 所以学习这些
shortcut keys shift and control is going
快捷键Shift和Control正在进行
to avoid some confusion in this mode
为了避免这种模式中的一些混乱
we'll go ahead and play with some of
我们将继续和一些
these different selection methods it may
这些不同的选择方法
not be clear right now how powerful this
现在还不清楚这有多强大
is but as we start using more of the
但是当我们开始使用更多的
color tools and some of the different
颜色工具和一些不同的
filters it's going to be really powerful
过滤器会非常强大
and understanding a good foundation
理解一个良好的基础
understanding how selection works is
理解选择是如何运作的
going to help you avoid a lot of
会帮助你避免很多
confusion and frustration in the future
未来的困惑和挫折
so go ahead and leave your question in
所以请把你的问题留在
the comments below if you have any and I
下面的评论如果你有任何和我
look forward to catching you in the next
期待着在下一个时刻赶上你
you
你